[dramatic music playing]
[missiles launching]
[bullet whooshing]
[radio chattering indistinctly]
[tracker beeping]
[explosion echoes]
[bullets whizzing]
[soldiers chattering
indistinctly]
[gun fires]
[gunshot echoes]
[dramatic music continues]
[guns firing]
[heroic music playing]
[clattering]
[guns firing]
[music fades]
- [alarm blaring]
- [gasps]
[alarm stops]
[somber music playing]
[spits]
- [worker] Boss. This for you.
- No, no, no. Come on.
I can't impose on your family.
No.
Yasmin, she made
this just for you.
Jefe, please.
Take it.
Tell her thank you.
Yeah.
So, listen.
Today's gonna be hard.
- [machinery beeping]
- We got inspections all day.
Forms to build,
forms to break down
and deliveries all
gettin' in our way.
- [drilling]
- We work hard today,
there'll be a bonus for ya.
[in Spanish] Understand?
[in English] And
let's all go home
with the same amount of
fingers that we came with.
- [workers clapping]
- [worker] All right.
- [worker] Hermanos.
-  [bell ringing]
[man] Have a good
day. Let's get it.
[hammering and drilling]
[inspirational music playing]
- Morning, Jess.
- Buenos dias, Levon.
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
- Gracias.
- [girl] Hey, Levon.
No one's been asking
you for money today?
No.
- Why?
- [sighs] Because, apparently,
I am the only
person in the family
who can do the
vendor accounting.
[woman] Oh, excuse me!
Hey, I guess we're evil
parents, babe, huh?
'Cause we make her
work a couple hours.
Not today.
How about you get those
disbursements done, huh?
We got a line of trucks
out there that need paying.
You could pay me.
Pay you for what?
For 19 years of free rent,
and groceries, and high school,
college, makeup, karate classes?
- You want me to keep goin'?
- Really? No. It's okay.
Levon, can you
sign that, please?
- Dad?
- What?
- Today is a total shitshow.
- I know.
And you scheduled
three things at once.
- She's not wrong.
- [chuckles]
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia
and Family Construction.
Yeah, you're
speaking with Carla,
you've had me on
hold for a bit now.
So, we're gettin' those
deliveries today, right?
[speaking Spanish]
[Carla] Yeah, I'll hold.
[in English] This is
what I need for tonight.
That's insane. What is that? Is
that for your wedding or something?
- [laughs]
- No, it's for tonight.
We finished the semester,
so we're gonna celebrate.
I mean, you just
finished one semester.
- Right. It's a big milestone.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Is that a thing?
Look, it could be worse, okay?
- Look, I'm passing the hat.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- That gets us a party van.
- Oh, my God.
Locks in a private
room for dinner.
Just saving like crazy.
[girl] Yeah. I just
need a card on file.
Mija, I can't. I don't...
[Carla] Mija...
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
Just give her what she wants.
No, Mom, I can fight
my own battles.
Oh, no, no, nobody's
arguing that.
[suspenseful music playing]
I mean, everybody needs
a party bus, right?
After they finish
one semester. Here.
Thank you.
[people chattering indistinctly]
Hey, Kate.
[goons shouting in Spanish]
[punches landing]
- [goon 1 shouts]
- [worker grunts]
[punching]
[nails rattling]
[cursing in Spanish]
Excuse me.
He needs to get back to work.
Get the fuck out of here.
It's not your business.
[worker] I'm good, boss.
All good. Five
minutes. [groans]
[goons grunting]
[goons yelling and grunting]
[thrilling music playing]
[yelps and whimpers]
[goon 3] Hey!
[suspenseful music playing]
[goons coughing]
[gun cocking]
[in Spanish] Hold on.
Put down your weapons.
[in English] I was respectful.
You weren't.
Get outta here. Get up.
Don't come back.
- Vamonos.
- [goon 2] Vamonos.
[suspenseful music continues]
You okay?
How did you do that?
[vehicles departing]
We need to get back to work.
[Levon] This one.
Over to the right.
- [Kate] You got it.
- Thanks, Kate.
Levon! Holy fuck!
Was that some military shit?
You didn't see anything.
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
[scoffs]
Can you teach me?
Look, my grandpa, he
was a paratrooper.
Taught me how to break fingers,
track animals.
Break fingers?
[chuckles] Yeah.
Grandma made you tinga.
Shredded chicken.
It's good.
And Grandma made you some
handmade grandma tortillas.
Why is everyone
always feeding me?
If we don't, you'll just eat
canned tuna and peanut butter.
You didn't see anything, okay?
Snitches get stitches.
Just get my back
if I ever need it.
Sure, Jenny.
[Jenny] See ya.
[captivating music playing]
[llama bellowing]
- [car engine stops]
- [seat belt clicks]
[bird squawking]
[people chattering indistinctly]
Love you, Daddy.
Love you, too, honey.
Get in the truck.
[birds squawking]
What's the occasion?
[man] No occasion.
Meredith's entertaining
some friends.
Yeah.
I didn't realize today
was your visitation.
You could let her stay.
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth,
we don't have to do this.
You weren't there when
her mother needed you
and you won't be there
when Meredith needs you,
but I will.
Oh, I know.
You want to strike me.
It's your only answer.
Violence.
You're an unsafe parent.
You're a killer.
You can't pretend
that you're not.
[somber music playing]
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
[car door opens, closes]
[sighs]
Today's my day.
Why's your grandfather
throwing a party on my day?
I'm super hungry.
I didn't eat.
I was waiting for you.
You were?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
[makes whooshing sound]
I don't need you buying stuff.
Come on. Open it.
It's Mama.
[sentimental music playing]
I took that picture
with a film camera
my dad gave me.
Grandpa took all of
Mama's pictures down.
Sometimes I forget
what she looks like.
She looks like you.
Dad, can I tell you something?
Anything.
I'm mad at Mama.
For dying and leaving us.
It's okay.
I hurt, too.
[sentimental music continues]
Matt will see you now.
He's throwing parties for her
during my visitation time.
Staring at me, laughing.
[Matt] He's baiting you.
Hoping you throw a punch.
Nah.
Then he wins.
Opposing counsel
alleges you have untreated PTSD
and brain trauma from
your military service,
making you at-risk for violence.
I served Britain, the country
of my birth, for 22 years.
I'm the fuckin' bad guy for it?
It gets worse.
They're requesting
supervised visits
and a reduction in visitation
from two hours a week
to one hour every two.
[Levon] I have to fight this.
I have ten grand saved up.
[Matt] From sleeping
in your truck?
Court won't be thrilled
by your lack of a
fixed residence.
Hey, I'll figure it out.
Why does Doctor Roth
hate you so much?
He thinks I killed his daughter.
Did you?
It was suicide.
I was overseas on a deployment.
She battled depression
her whole life.
You've heard of
attrition warfare?
Yeah. You grind the
enemy down slowly.
This guy's got a team
of thousand-dollar-an-hour
attorneys
who will bleed you dry
until you turn to
dust and blow away.
The best we can do is
negotiated surrender.
You have a daughter?
[somber music playing]
[siren wailing]
[hip-hop music playing]
[girls cheering]
I got you guys a
little somethin'.
Nina.
Jocelyn...
- Chantel. And Rubi.
- Thanks, Mama.
Dude, these are insane!
Where'd you get these?
I have a cousin. Or seven.
Salud, bitches!
[all cheering]
[hip-hop music
continues over speakers]
[all cheering]
[door creaking]
[pensive music playing]
Thank you.
- [tv switch clicks]
- [static buzzing]
[metal creaking]
[pensive music continues]
- [Nina] Shots.
- [all laughing]
[upbeat music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[party music playing]
[both cheering]
[woman] Hey!
[man] What? What? What?
What the fuck are
we still doing here?
He said he wants the One.
"I want the One. I
want the fucking One."
What the fuck does that mean?
He'll know it when
he sees her, okay?
Do you know how
much fuckin' money
we're gonna make on this?
- We better.
- Enjoy, yeah?
- [all cheering]
- [upbeat folk music playing]
Hey, last establishment.
You guys have early flights.
[wind blowing]
[pop music playing
over speakers]
[people chattering indistinctly]
Is that back table open?
It's yours if you
tell me your name.
It's Jenny.
Hi, I'm Johnny.
Hi, Johnny.
Right here.
[pop music continues]
[phone chimes]
[ominous music playing]
My man.
[Jenny] You are more
than a pitch deck.
[girls laugh]
- [Nina groans softly]
- Nina?
- Nina, don't throw up.
- I'm fine.
She's making her puke face.
- Let's get you to a bathroom.
- [Rubi] Oh, ew.
Cheap! Bad energy.
[ominous music continues]
[coughing]
[Jenny] Ew!
- [Jenny laughs]
- Oh, my God.
I hate you so much right
now, it's not funny.
It's kinda funny.
[Nina groans, sniffles]
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
I cannot go out there like this.
Okay, well, pick your battles,
'cause we're leavin' in 30.
- [door unlocks]
- [toilet flushes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[muffled grunting]
[Jenny struggling]
Fuck!
[Jenny whimpering]
[woman] Go.
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music continues]
[music fades]
[police radio
chattering indistinctly]
Jenny's missing.
What do you mean, "missing"?
[somber music playing]
She went out with her
friends on Friday.
Saturday, we were worried,
so we called the cops,
and then on Sunday...
She had a piano recital
on Sunday night.
We invited half our family.
My cousin Dinora is a
Police Captain in Philly,
and she says they
don't work these cases.
They take a report
and forget about it.
Can you help us?
I can keep the site
running smoothly.
No. Help us find Jen.
My dad was a Green Beret.
I can see you guys
comin' a mile away.
You hunt bad guys.
You jump outta planes.
[tearfully] And you
get those bad guys.
I'm a different person now.
All right, well,
[sniffles] maybe
this'll help her.
Here, it's 50.
Take it.
[Carla] We have another
20 for expenses.
Come on, just take it, man.
[Levon] I'm sorry.
It's not who I am anymore.
[pensive music playing]
[arrow whizzes]
Gunny, it's me!
Don't kill me!
I got steaks!
If you'd shot a foot to
the left, I'd be dead.
If I wanted you
dead, you'd be dead.
[laughs]
You know, for me,
there's no separation
between day and night.
So, I got to make my own.
It's hard livin'
in a gray world.
I couldn't save your eyes.
Sorry.
That eats at me.
No.
You saved my life.
Joyce would be burying
tags in the back yard
if you hadn't come along,
scooped me up and ran.
[somber music playing]
What's her name?
Jenny.
Jenny. All right.
She a good kid?
She's a great kid.
Now, you do this,
you better lock in.
You better go full
on, no half-measures.
But you do, God
help 'em. [chuckles]
I told Jenny I had her back.
Well, uh...
I miss ya.
I worry about ya,
but you didn't have to come
down here and pretend that
you needed my
permission for something
you already made
your mind up about.
[both chuckle]
[bell dinging]
[woman] Get in
here. We're eating.
[engine revving in distance]
[people chattering indistinctly]
Hey, Carla.
Thanks for coming.
Where is he?
Upstairs. First
door on your left.
[sighs heavily]
["Moonlight Sonata" by
Ludwig van Beethoven playing]
[Jenny playing "Moonlight
Sonata" on piano]
"Moonlight Sonata".
- Yeah.
- It's beautiful.
She turned down a
music scholarship
to go to business school.
[sniffles]
[voice breaking] She
wanted to be like her pops.
[breath trembling]
Be a big land developer.
And she will.
Yeah.
Nah. No, thanks.
Your family needs hope.
But I can't face 'em like this.
When my wife passed,
and I left the Royal Marines,
a lot of people
would've given up on me.
But you were patient with me.
- You, Carla, Jenny.
- Jenny.
You're my family.
[somber music fades in]
Look at me, brother.
I'm gonna bring her home.
[resolute music playing]
I promise.
I'm gonna bring her home.
[suspenseful music playing]
[alarm blaring in distance]
[dramatic music playing]
[Levon] "Skip's Bar."
[camera beeps]
- [people chattering indistinctly]
- [house music playing]
Thank you very
much. Good, bro?
You good? Yeah?
How you doing?
You need a little
aperitif, you know?
All right.
[Johnny speaking indistinctly]
[house music continues, muffled]
[suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[zips pouch]
[keypad beeping]
[keypad chimes]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [car lock chimes]
[engine starts]
[tracker beeping]
[dramatic music playing]
[liquid bubbling]
[dog barking in distance]
[dog barking]
[tracker beeping]
[beeping stops]
[lock clicking, unlocks]
[inhaling]
[rock music playing on tv]
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
Get the fuck out.
Hello, Johnny.
Wanna have a race?
See who wins?
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [shotgun cocking]
Hands up. Stand up.
Place your fingers
behind your head.
You a cop?
You wish I was a cop.
[sputters, scoffs]
Your adventure, kid.
Where's the girl?
What girl?
The missing girl.
The one your friends snatched
outta the back of the bar.
I told the cops. She ran
off. Drunk or somethin'.
Fuckin' poobutt
can't hold her drink.
How's that my problem?
- People lie.
- [liquid bubbling]
Do you lie, Johnny?
[exhales]
I don't trust people.
I trust biology.
- We're all wired the same.
- [Johnny scoffs]
Get the fuck up.
[Johnny grunting, muffled]
[muffled grunting]
[gasping]
Fuck you. [groans]
Your mind knows
you're in the bathtub
and it's just a wet towel.
But adrenaline makes
your heart race,
- so you burn more air.
- [breathing heavily]
Your nervous system tells
you that you're drowning.
Your bosses know you deal
dope over the bar top?
Steal from the till?
Fuck you!
[Johnny screaming, muffled]
[Johnny choking]
[faucet squeaks]
[gasping loudly]
[Johnny] You know these
guys are next level.
They wipe out entire
fucking bloodlines.
Fair enough.
Just know you're
giving me names.
Your choice how.
[man] Johnny?
Where are you, brother?
[suspenseful music playing]
You're expecting company?
Damn fuckin' right,
I am. [screaming]
Open the door.
Fuckin' kill you.
[screams]
[fabric rips]
Russians.
Fuck.
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
[engine revving in distance]
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry for...
shielding myself...
in a blanket of accomplishments.
I wish you could've seen me...
who I really am.
Just want to be strong like you.
[train horn blaring]
[suspenseful music playing]
[camera beeping]
[menacing music playing]
[dogs barking]
What am I doing here?
[man] on speaker It's better
you see for yourself, boss.
It's not a big problem.
[speaking Russian]
[in English] What the fuck
have you two done, huh?
[door closes]
Why'd they shoot each other?
This is very unprofessional.
Johnny has no control.
He's a weak man.
Maybe he talk crazy, and
then it's bang-bang time.
- "Bang-bang time"?
- Yeah.
Bang-bang time.
You notice anything different?
Your hair.
- [slaps]
- Idiot.
Where is my fucking money?
You think this was a robbery?
Impossible.
No one would rob us.
No one is that stupid,
or that crazy.
This is a shotgun wound.
You see any shotguns?
- Hmm?
- That's nine bands missing.
Ninety thousand dollars
of our fucking money!
It's Symon's money.
[in Russian] May your blood
purify the soil, comrade.
[suspenseful music playing]
[woman speaking Spanish]
[phone ringing]
- [phone chimes]
- Hey, sweetheart.
Hey, Daddy, what are you doing?
Uh, nothin'. Just, uh...
Just some work.
- Are you in school?
- Yeah.
You supposed to be
calling me from school?
No.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I just wanted to
say, "hi." Love you, Daddy.
Love you, too.
Bye.
[door opens]
[dog barking]
[suspenseful music builds]
The fucking door opens itself?
[curses in Russian]
[car door closes]
[suspenseful music continues]
[in Russian]
Everything is fucked!
[dramatic music playing]
[camera beeps]
I don't like this.
I'm alone in the bed all night.
You eat.
You come to bed for a bit.
- [slaps]
- [woman yelps, gasps]
[woman speaking
Russian over speakers]
You think the money
falls from the sky?
- Hmm?
- [woman breathing heavily]
[knife clatters]
[in Russian] Bastard.
[car lock chirps]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [screams]
- [Levon grunts]
[objects clattering]
[toaster dings]
[Levon] Hope you don't mind.
[crunching]
I was hungry.
Thought we could
have a little chat.
I'm gonna take the tape off.
But if you can't
control your volume...
- [man grunts]
- [chains rattle]
You go in the water.
Do you know who I am?
Should I?
You clearly have no
idea who you fuck with.
[scoffs] Make yourself
happy. Tell me.
[speaking Russian]
[in English] You
have heard of us?
I have.
Really?
The Vor.
The Bratva. The Brothers.
The League of Thieves.
Whatever Russian gangsters
like to call
themselves these days.
You clearly are somebody.
You slaughter Vory soldiers.
You steal Vory money.
It was a misunderstanding.
I am a brother of high rank.
You and all connected with you,
will be hunted for
three generations.
Yep. I assumed so.
We all know how
these things play out
if you don't keep them tidy.
- Fuck you!
- [slap echoes]
That's for slapping
that woman this morning.
That woman was my wife.
[slap echoes]
That's for slapping your wife.
[unzips pouch]
Here's your money.
I'm not a thief.
I don't care about
your business.
I'm lookin' for a young lady.
[man speaking Russian]
[in English] I...
I don't understand.
The bar you do your
dirty business out of,
a 19 year-old girl
was kidnapped.
I'm lookin' for her.
Dimi.
[speaking Russian]
[gasps]
Maybe you should
keep your voice down.
What do you want?
Gimme the girl,
and everybody goes
about their business.
A girl?
All of this is for a girl?
No one kills three
people to sell a woman.
No one.
I'm not selling her.
I'm gonna bring her home.
Not stopping until I do.
Who are you?
[suspenseful music playing]
What are you?
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Okay, we're done.
[man yelping]
[unsettling music playing]
[muffled screaming]
[music fades]
[sighs heavily]
- [phone beeps]
- [man speaks Russian on phone]
[ominous music playing]
Dimi.
Who are you, Dimi?
[zips body bag]
- [tense music playing]
- [woman speaks indistinctly]
[tense music continues]
[ominous music playing]
[in Russian] Father.
[Symon in English]
He takes money.
He leaves money.
He kills without fear.
The question is why?
Wolo was a respected
man of honor,
but his son was never like us.
Dimi is not a businessman.
He prefers mischief
over hard work.
He spits on his father's
heart every fucking day.
Find this man.
- [Wolo screaming]
- [Levon grunts]
And bring him to me.
[ominous music playing]
[scraping]
[keys jangling]
[cell door opens]
My name is Jenny Garcia.
My father is Joe.
My mother is Carla.
You have the wrong
girl. This is a mistake.
[woman] They're not real.
You're not real.
This...
is fucking real.
[sinister music playing]
Eat your fuckin' food,
then you put on
the fucking clothes
- and shut the fuck up!
- Fuck you!
[woman] Have you ever
seen someone die before?
Huh?
Their eyes just
cloud right over.
Mmm. You're so
fuckin' pretty. Huh?
Aren't you, Princess?
Aw.
Boop.
Eat your fuckin' food!
[cell door closes]
[announcer 1 on radio]
Believe the idea the
White Sox are in serious talks
to build a new stadium in
the South Loops, The 78,
the location by the Chicago
River just off Roosevelt.
[announcer 2] I love the idea
of being in serious talks
for a new stadium
in the South Loop.
[phone buzzing]
[chuckles]
How's it goin', cat?
Getting rich contracting?
Oh, yeah. Pouring
concrete more like.
I'm outta the game. I'm
an honest taxpayer now.
[chuckles] You talked to
Gunny? How's he doing?
Saw him the other
day. He's happy.
Well, you never call me
unless you need something,
so, what do you want?
Lookin' for someone called Dimi.
Probably Dimitri. An associate
of Wolodymyr Kolisnyk.
That's a high-ranking dude, cat.
Mafia captain.
Legit Bratva shot caller.
Not a guy you wanna fuck with.
Nah, never.
This Dimi fella,
he might be involved
in human trafficking.
Can you check NADDIS and NCIC?
See if you can get a hit?
I gotta be careful,
but there's a bar called
Hattie's in Joliet,
where they sell meth
for the Russians.
Maybe you should
get a beer there.
Nice one. Thanks.
[dramatic music builds]
[country music playing]
Hey. Whatcha havin'?
I'll just have a
beer. You pick.
Okay.
[country music
continues over speakers]
[camera beeping]
[door opens, closes]
[man] Oh, hey, stranger.
Where you been?
Tryin' to make a buck.
[man] You know,
rumor has it you and
your shitbag brother
have been talkin'
to the Russians.
Rumor has it you were so high,
you accidentally killed
Big Mike in a trap house
and blamed it on a robbery crew.
Fuckin' shut up. Fuckin'...
Dutch finds out anybody's
talkin' to the Russians but him,
he's gonna lose
his fuckin' mind.
Shh!
[country music
playing over speakers]
Do you know this guy?
No. I've never seen him.
[woman] I don't like him.
Looks like a cop.
[camera whirring]
[woman] He's got a
gun in his pocket.
Like a .38. You see it?
Fuck. Yes.
You're up, kid.
[country music continues]
[man whistling]
[slams glass]
[continues whistling]
Follow me.
[country music continues]
Go talk to the man.
You lookin' for somethin'?
My interests are strictly
pharmaceutical, brother.
Any reason why you
packin' heat, brah?
I'm carrying money.
Hate to lose it to
a man with a knife.
He's a cop.
Are you a cop?
Nah. Are you?
[snickering]
Run your pockets, Chief.
Let's check for that badge.
[man] You heard the man.
Put it on the table.
Fuckin' now.
I didn't come here
to be disrespected.
[upbeat music playing]
All right.
[exhales]
Let's play.
Get him.
[henchmen grunting and yelling]
[exhales]
[Levon grunting]
- [henchman 1 yelling]
- [metal clangs]
[men clamoring]
[henchman 2 groans in pain]
[screams in pain]
Get him, brother.
- [woman shrieks]
- [bottles clatter]
[henchman 3 yells]
[screams]
Bye, asshole.
Enough!
- [upbeat music fades]
- [bottles clinking]
[foreboding music playing]
[footsteps thudding]
[bottle shatters]
My grandpa told me to
never shake hands sittin'.
[hands clap]
[Dutch] Look at those bricks.
You ain't a cop,
you're a working man.
Been in construction
my whole life.
Were you a soldier?
'Cause you fight like a soldier.
I did my part.
I was Airborne.
They trained us to
jump outta planes
and we ended up ridin'
a bus into combat.
[chuckles] Sounds about right.
Have a seat, brother.
I heard you're in a buyin' mood.
I'm lookin' for blue glass,
the good stuff.
I need weight. Regular.
Like four pounds a month.
That's all?
Who you flippin' it to?
It goes where it's needed.
The customers are my
concern, not yours.
And why here? Why us?
My Chicago connect
is missin' in action.
I'm runnin' work
crews in shifts 24/7.
Time is money.
Seven K for half a pound.
That's a Chicago price.
Five.
There's a pancake house
at the highway junction
straight north of here.
Be there, 7:00 a.m.,
having breakfast.
And?
And bring five stacks.
Good talk.
Now get the fuck outta here.
[suspenseful music playing]
Have a seat.
[man] Mm.
This is like an awkward
Tinder date. [snickers]
Just give her the money.
[sinister music playing]
[woman] Mmm. Lo, and behold.
People talk,
money fucks.
You got somethin' for me?
We don't know who the
fuck you are, brother.
You'll get a call tellin'
you where your shit is.
That's it?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Don't play me.
I know where to find you.
Yeah. I guess you do.
Thank you for not shooting me.
[mimics gunshot]
[man] fuckin' asshole.
[dramatic music playing]
[phone ringing]
- Yeah?
- [Dutch] All right. You ready?
I'm gonna tell you where
the skante's at, big dog.
I'm waitin'.
Under your seat.
- Thank you.
- Keep the burner phone.
I'mma hit you tomorrow.
Then you can tell me
how y'all motherfuckers
built Rome in a day off my shit.
Then we can talk about weight.
- [line disconnects]
- [phone beeps]
[dramatic music continues]
[unzips bag]
[woman] Guess who's gonna
be princess for a night?
[soft music playing
over speakers]
You are Dimi's
miracle workers. Huh?
And that, that is
for Dimi's miracle.
Why her?
She reminded me of a painting
in one of my father's houses.
Take her in the back.
Sure.
[ominous music playing]
[heart thumping]
[exhales]
[gargling]
Look how cute these ones are.
They look like little sharks.
Just like you, cutie.
[laughs]
[eerie music playing]
She bit me!
[grunts]
She's supposed to be asleep!
I'm so sorry, sir.
I want her out!
[tense music playing]
[yells]
[train chugging]
[phone ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Yeah?
Did they like my shit?
Let's just say
they were pleased.
There's plenty more
where that came from,
but there's someone
you gotta check in with
if we're gonna do business.
What does that mean?
Precautionary measures, brah.
Seein' as the Feds are handin'
out life sentences per pound.
Yeah, this game's
not for everyone.
I hear you, big dog.
I'mma shoot you an
invite for a sit-down.
Bring your money
and wear a suit.
I don't have a suit.
Shit. You will tomorrow.
'Cause these motherfuckers
are as high power as it gets.
[new age music
playing over speakers]
I'm here to see
someone called Dutch.
He's right this way.
He's over there.
- How you doin'?
- Hey, Dutch.
You bring the money?
May I?
First, you gotta
turn your phone off.
[phone shuts down]
Now what?
You already have my money.
I came here in good
faith to do business.
My name is Dimi.
[suspenseful music playing]
Yours?
Bill.
Bill Coates.
Do you have driver's
license, Bill Coates?
Excuse me?
It's fine. Let him check.
You drive rental.
We check plates.
Tax write-off.
That okay?
This man is my business partner.
He is small potatoes.
I am the big potatoes.
Tell me.
Will you be a problem?
Is this how you do business?
You invite me here
to be threatened?
Checks out.
I apologize for
that, "William."
You are clearly a...
serious person.
[chuckling]
If you need resupply,
use the burner.
Text bunny rabbit emoji.
Bunny rabbit emoji.
You made aware I need
four pounds a month?
Oh.
Then text eggplant emoji.
[laughs]
We are aware.
If you like what is in the case,
we do more business.
Now, you leave and
don't look back.
Fine by me.
[dramatic music playing]
Johnny, you're a
real piece of shit.
[thrilling music playing]
[engines revving]
You sneaky motherfucker.
[camera whirring]
Hi, asshole.
Hmm.
[line ringing]
He's here.
- Oh, shit.
- [woman] on speakers He's in a black Dodge Ram
hiding in the trees.
[man] Okay, we're
pulling up now.
Let's go!
[thrilling music continues]
[shouts in Russian]
[men shouting in Russian]
Fuck! He just fuckin'
left on a bike! Go!
[men shouting in Russian]
[in English] Go! Go! Go!
Fuck!
[dramatic music playing]
[man shouting in Russian]
[shouting in Russian]
[guns firing]
[tires screech]
[man shouting in Russian]
[bullet clangs]
- [motorcycle screeching]
- [grunts]
[siren wailing]
[groaning]
[police radio chattering]
[grunts]
Show me your hands.
Hey.
You didn't see us here.
Nothing fucking happened.
[man 2] We'll take it from here.
You're on the payroll too?
[man 2 speaking Russian]
[suspenseful music playing]
[door slams]
[Levon groans]
[man] How do you know Dimi?
What is your business with Dimi?
Ah, you two assholes.
[man] That man you drowned,
in his own pool while
his wife was at Pilates,
that man was our uncle.
He wouldn't shut up.
I warned him.
- Do you know who we are, hmm?
- Hey. Hey.
Yeah, people whose
ma dresses 'em funny.
This is fucking couture, man.
It's our fucking brand!
Tie up his legs.
If you want me to be scared,
you gotta try harder.
[all grunting]
- [brakes screech]
- [man] Whoa!
[both grunting]
[tires screeching]
[man choking]
[in Russian, weakly]
Kill this demon.
[man 2 yelling]
[tires screeching]
[man 1 coughing]
[all grunting]
[all yelping]
[van screeching]
[man 2 choking]
- [Levon grunting]
- [man 1 groaning]
- [Levon growls]
- [screaming]
- [shouts in Russian]
- [guns firing]
[gun fires]
[van creaking]
- [grunts]
- [van sliding]
[bubbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
That is Vanko.
And that is Danya.
These are my sons.
My house and my lineage end
on these cold, steel tables.
Convene the war counsel.
[ominous music builds]
[trance music playing]
Excuse me, dear.
Fuck off.
Oh, wow.
Absolutely fuckin' not.
Oh, fuck.
You're lucky you're
not already dead.
Dimi, apologies, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm
truly fuckin' sorry.
She fucking bit
half his face off.
- It wasn't exactly half his face. But...
- Oh. [laughs]
Thirty-six stitches.
That's a lot.
To reattach his cheek.
I am in the business of
pleasure, not surgery.
Tell me...
[sinister music playing]
[man] Fuck.
Do you know what business means?
Do I... No. I
mean, yeah. Fuck.
[Dimi] Business means
you keep your word.
You deliver promises.
You make customer happy.
Not bite fucking face off!
- Understood.
- No.
You just fucked me
out of 200 grand.
If you make one, I make two.
[man breathing nervously]
Customer wants her
dead. I want her dead.
You kill her. You know
where to take her.
Consider it done.
Now fuck off!
Fucking off, sir.
Holy shit, he was pissed.
Fucking beyond. He was this
close to smokin' us both.
We gotta whack that girl.
Fine by me. Let's
do the little bitch.
We are facing a devil.
This devil kills two soldiers.
He drowns Wolodymyr,
an esteemed captain.
Now he kills my sons.
You do understand my concern?
Where is Dimi?
Won't he know who this devil is?
Dimi's hiding.
[ominous music playing]
They will help you find Dimi.
Thank you for bringing
this to my attention.
Now go.
[ominous music continues]
[club music playing]
[people chattering indistinctly]
[woman grunts]
[crowd screaming]
[mysterious guitar
music playing]
- Some champagne?
- [grunts loudly]
[foreboding music playing]
Your father is dead.
Tied to a chair
and drowned in his pool.
So, it's good news.
The man who killed him
murdered my sons.
Danya and Vanko?
What the fuck?
You did not know this?
How the fuck would I know?
Nobody tells me anything.
The Brotherhood treats
me like I'm radioactive.
[Symon] Who is this man?
[suspenseful music builds]
I ask with kindness.
- [gun thuds]
- [crowd exclaims]
I bankroll biker gang
with meth connection.
They introduce me to
buyer with real cash.
We met for five minutes.
That's it.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
I have this.
He's hunting you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[crowd panicking]
[chiming]
[hacker] Found him.
[ominous music playing]
[instructor speaking
indistinctly on TV]
[Roth] Oh.
[Roth breathes deeply]
[relaxing music playing]
[exhales]
[tense music builds]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [woman] Hi. Mr. Cade?
This is the Main Office.
Um, no one's come to
pick up Meredith today.
I'll be right there.
[school bell ringing]
- Hey.
- Good day?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
[train horn blares]
Where's Grandpa?
He's never late.
He's not answering me.
I sent him, like, 20 messages.
I'm sure he's fine.
You didn't kill him, did you?
Dad, I'm kidding.
Do you trust me?
Yeah.
So, if I tell you something,
you know you can
believe me, right?
Okay, the build-up is
just making it worse.
I made a big mistake.
Oh, my God. You
did kill Grandpa.
Merry, I'm serious.
Some really bad
people are after me,
and I don't want anyone
I love to get hurt.
Are you sharing your
location with Grandpa?
Yeah.
Can you see his location?
Maybe, I don't know.
Daddy, he's at home.
[tires screech]
[engine revving]
- [siren wailing in distance]
- [tense music playing]
Merry, stay here, okay?
Merry! Stay there!
Daddy, be careful!
[slams door]
- [tense music continues]
- [smoke alarm blaring]
[breathing nervously]
[flames roaring]
[Roth coughing]
[Levon grunting]
[siren wailing]
[coughing]
[Roth] Who were they?
Russian mafia?
Yes.
They were looking for you.
This happened because of you.
Violence follows
you like a cloud.
He could've left you
in there, Grandpa.
He saved your life.
I can acknowledge that.
You should go to the hospital.
You'll be safe there.
I'll take care of Merry.
[Roth] It's time o let
the cops handle this.
Cops can't stop them.
All right.
We'll figure it out later.
And, Levon,
thank you.
[people chattering indistinctly]
[Merry sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
You remember Gunny?
Your blind friend who
doesn't know he's blind?
That's the one.
He has a country house.
We'll be safe there
till the storm passes.
Hi.
You wanna come
inside? Come on.
- You hungry?
- Always.
- And you?
- [Merry] Yeah.
What happened, man?
You fuck with the
wrong people, huh?
Hey, you could've stopped me.
What force on earth
is gonna stop you?
It's gettin' ugly.
Can you find this girl? Can
you really find this girl?
I can find her.
I'm gonna bring her home.
I hear that. You got a plan?
I'm gonna ask this Dimi
fella where she is.
All roads lead to him.
Now, you killed
your way into this,
you're gonna have to
kill your way out of it.
I figured as much.
I can help you with that.
Oh, yeah?
Let me show you somethin'.
- [keypad beeping]
- [door unlocks, opens]
After you, sir.
All right, I will be
your weapons sommelier
for this evening.
If you come around this wall,
you see the Avtomat Kalashnikov,
been killing
Americans since 1947.
Also, comes in a deluxe,
blingy version pulled direct
from Saddam's palace.
What you got over here
is the M-Four Carbine,
it's the Chevy Impala
of the war on terror.
Beautiful MP5 SD here if
you wanna kill somebody,
but you don't wanna wake 'em up.
But this is the real beast here.
One of the original weapons of
the four horsemen
of the apocalypse.
The M14.
You might remember this weapon.
I don't want to, but I do.
There you go.
[solemn music playing]
I'll have to drill out
the serial numbers.
Oh, no, that's already done.
These were never
here. Never anywhere.
Kinda like us,
back in the day.
[chuckles] We did some
righteous shit, brother.
Yeah, we did.
- What's in there?
- None of your business.
Can I come?
Absolutely not.
What about school?
You'll miss a couple
of days, at most.
[Velcro rips]
I barely see you.
I don't want you
getting in trouble.
Then I'll never see you.
That's not gonna happen.
See this? This is you.
Half and half.
I want you to hold onto this.
I'm comin' back for that.
Okay.
[sentimental music playing]
I love you.
Love you, Daddy.
[kisses]
Daddy, I don't want
you getting hurt.
I'll be back soon, okay?
Gunny, take good care of her.
Yeah, of course.
- Thank you, Joyce.
- This way.
- Bye, Levon.
- All right, sweetheart.
[resolute music playing]
"Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done."
God ain't here, sweetheart.
- [gasps]
- Have a nice nap, Princess?
We gotta pull over
and load this bitch
with some fuckin'
sleeping pills...
- [woman grunts]
- [man] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- [woman] Fucking bitch!
- [man] Hey, take it easy!
- Pull over!
- [man] Come on! Stop!
Fucking get it, fucking bitch.
Fucking grab that bitch!
Pull over! Pull
over! Pull over!
- [crashing]
- [Jenny grunts]
[man groaning]
[woman] God damn it!
Where's my fucking gun!
- [man] Fuck!
- [Jenny screams]
[dramatic music playing]
- Fuck.
- [water splashing]
[grunts]
[woman] Fuckin' move, Viper!
[dramatic music continues]
[panting]
[bullets whizzing]
[woman] Fuck! Fuck!
I mean, what the fuck?
She is fast.
We're going back
to fuckin' prison!
[angrily] Huh?
Huh? You get it?
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
Fuck! Okay, okay.
Fuck! Fuck!
Shit.
[somber music playing]
Okay, genius,
now what?
[siren chirps]
[police radio chatter]
[Jenny breathing heavily]
Are you all right?
My name is Jenny
Garcia. I was kidnapped.
It's all right. We
know who you are.
Let's get you home.
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm so fucking sorry.
[tapping]
[unsettling music playing]
Miss me?
[woman] Fuck!
Fucking dome the bitch!
[phone ringing]
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Is that him?
What the fuck?
Fuck, it's a video call.
Here, take the fucking
phone! Give me the...
- Fuck!
- ...God damn fucking gun.
Hey, sir.
Dimi says you still
have the girl.
[Viper] Uh, yeah,
yeah. We still got her.
Show me she's still alive.
See? Still alive.
I want a second date
tonight, at the farmhouse.
One million dollars.
Uh, yeah. Whatever
you want, sir.
I'll get her cleaned up and
smelling real pretty for you.
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
Not sleepy,
but dirty and alive.
- For now.
-  [phone chimes]
- [woman] Fuck, yeah.
- [laughs] Oh, yes.
[Dimi] Which passport, okay?
You sent me all these passports.
I can't tell.
Red? Blue? Green?
[man speaking indistinctly]
- [Dimi] I don't know what color, just tell me.
- [woman] Where are we going?
What? Okay. Yeah. Go.
I take all of them, okay?
[snorting]
-What do you want? You want money?
-No, I don't...
Here, take your
money. You take money.
I don't want your fucking money!
- You take all the money.
- I don't want
- your fucking money!
- You take all the money, okay?
- [woman] Let me help you!
- No, no, I don't need help.
Fuck.
Get away! Stop!
[Dimi] Starting
tomorrow, rehab.
All you do is let me
slip down slippery slope.
- [guard grunting]
- [stabs knife]
[Dimi] You're supposed
to be my rock.
You know, like they say,
"Oh, she's my rock."
"Hey, thank you." I have
nothing to thank you for.
[tense music playing]
[knife slicing]
[guard on radio, in Russian]
Something's going on out there.
[Dimi in English] You know
what? You are just an enabler.
- [stabs knife]
- [blood splatters]
- [device crackling]
- [guard 3] he's here!
[device beeping rapidly]
[both gasping]
[guard 4 groaning]
[guns firing]
[guard 5 yelling]
[Dimi] Okay.
Okay. You made your point.
Now we make a
deal, and you begin
a new life as a
wealthy man, huh?
I can pay my own bills.
Congrats.
- Come closer and she dies.
- No!
I figured that.
[Dimi screaming]
You should disappear.
Take the money.
[Dimi groaning in pain]
Make a nice life.
Where is she?
[laughs smugly]
I do not know this woman.
You're a bad liar.
Why risk everything?
Why kill everyone for her?
'Cause I told her
I had her back.
If I give you this woman,
you let me live?
Because if I just
give you the address,
then you shoot me, huh?
What if you give me a fake
address and I shoot you?
That's bad for both of us.
Head south on 57.
Then I give you her address.
Let's go.
[Levon] You know this guy?
Of course, I know. He's Viper.
He's Chief of Human
Resource Department
and recruiting for
special projects.
Why you do all this for a whore?
[Levon grunts]
[coughs]
Say it again.
Please, say that again.
[Dimi groaning]
Thought so.
Okay, Dimi,
tell me where we're going.
Where is she?
There.
[somber music playing]
- [Dimi groaning]
- [knife slices]
[Levon] She's in there?
She's there.
- [gun cocks]
- Promise?
I promise.
She's there.
[Dimi panting]
Why her?
Who decides?
[Dimi spits]
Viper goes to club,
takes pictures of pretty girls.
I send them to clients,
they make choice.
Meeting is arranged.
This is my specialty service.
Like shopping for a
set of snow tires.
These are human beings.
[in Russian] You
must be kidding.
[in English] You think
money gives a shit
where it comes from?
If I didn't do this,
somebody else would.
You still haven't told me why.
Why do you hunt us?
You have a daughter?
No.
Then you won't understand.
[Dimi groans]
[somber music playing]
[people chattering indistinctly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
[melancholy music playing]
[playing "Moonlight Sonata"]
["Moonlight Sonata" continues]
- [branches rustling]
- [body thuds]
Hey, good lookin' out.
Hey, yo, we good, brother?
Man, we far from good.
That motherfucker we
hooked up with Dimi
clapped out half a
dozen Russians tonight.
Rumor is, he's on his way to
Dimi's trap house right now.
[cylinder whirring]
Everybody,
mount the fuck up!
[man] You heard
the man. Mount up!
[tense music playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
[tense music continues]
[door creaking, opens]
[both laughing]
That's funny shit.
- [knife slices]
- [guard screams]
[continues playing
"Moonlight Sonata"]
Sounds lovely, Princess.
[Jenny sighs]
[tense music continues]
I don't condone this behavior,
but my bank account does.
[handcuffs clicking]
Hey. It's time.
What the fuck are we
still doing here? Come on.
Yeah. I'll get the pervert.
We're all just numbers,
kid. Nothin' personal.
Feels pretty fuckin'
personal to me.
- [dramatic music playing]
- [engines revving]
[tokens clinking]
We have to go now, sir.
Why?
It's now or never.
Then it's now.
[ominous music playing]
What have I done to you?
Nothing.
That's the best part.
I wonder what you
look like on...
the inside.
[dramatic music continues]
[people chattering indistinctly]
[grenade clicks]
[grenade clatters]
[guards screaming]
- [building rumbles]
- The fuck was that?
- [Viper] whoa.
- [guests screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
[guests screaming]
[guns firing]
Levon!
[woman] Are they
fucking shooting?
[Jenny] Who's gonna
get fucked now, huh?
[women screaming]
[men panicking]
[engines revving]
[tense music playing]
[guard] He's in there.
Shooting the place up.
Everybody,
lock and load.
Let's go get this motherfucker.
Yeah, you two on me.
You heard the man. Come on.
Stay tight, stay right.
Demon, put it through the glass.
[Demon] You got it.
[engine revving]
[engine roars]
Levon!
- Shut the fuck up!
- [muffled grunting]
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
Yeah?
[hesitates] You just... Yeah.
I'm beginning to think
that you do not know
what you are doing!
Don't worry, sir.
Everything's under control.
I promise you.
[tense music continues]
- [man yells]
- [knife clangs]
I'm gonna cut your heart out.
Good luck.
[both grunting]
[stabs knife]
[Dutch yells]
What the fuck is your real name?
Levon.
Nice to meet you, Levon.
You ready, son?
I'm always ready.
[yells]
[Dutch groans]
My fight wasn't with you.
[weakly] I know, brother.
Finish it.
- [flesh squelches]
- [screams]
[Dutch groans]
[body thuds]
[somber music playing]
Sorry, brother.
[dramatic music playing]
[rifle clicking]
- [Jenny] Levon!
- [woman] What the fuck?
[dramatic music builds]
How dare you come in here?
[man screams]
- Fuck! Shit!
- [Viper] Oh, fuck!
Oh, that is not good.
- [gun clicking]
- What the fuck?
- Hang on.
- [woman] Reload!
- [Viper] wait, wait, wait.
- [gun clatters]
No, no, no!
- I can explain everything!
- [woman] Fuck!
No!
[Viper groaning]
[woman groans]
Oh, shit.
[Viper grunts]
Mommy!
- Fuck!
- [Jenny grunting]
Fuck!
Fuckin' bitch!
Fuck.
Fuck you!
[Viper groaning]
[blood dripping]
It's over now.
Fucking die, bitch!
[woman choking]
[Jenny grunting]
[neck snaps]
[panting]
[ominous music playing]
[radio chattering indistinctly]
[guns cocking]
I think I killed her.
Good.
[pipes clanging]
Fuck.
Whoa.
Stay on my six.
What's that mean?
Follow me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[siren wailing]
There's an active
shooter in there.
[siren continues wailing]
[officers screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
- [yelps]
- Shit.
Let's kill this guy.
[gunfire continues]
What was that?
Bluetooth.
- [grenade clicks]
- Is that a grenade?
Mind your ears.
[grenade pin clatters]
[sighs] Oh.
[screaming]
You ready?
No.
Time to go.
[triumphant music playing]
See you on the other side.
[Levon sighs]
What was that?
Respect for an old friend.
[triumphant music continues]
[dramatic music playing]
You ready to go home?
- Get me the hell outta here.
- [engine revs]
[triumphant music resumes]
[music fades]
[line ringing]
Yes, my brother.
He escaped...
with the girl.
None of this was business.
The devil has what he came for.
Let him go.
I understand our need to
move quietly in the world.
But I will not turn
the other cheek
to the man who
killed my children.
Then we will kill you.
The Brotherhood comes before
your personal vengeance.
Do you understand?
I understand.
[ominous music playing]
[screaming]
[birds chirping]
Hey...
snitches get stitches.
[solemn music playing]
- [people chattering
indistinctly] - [door closes]
[Carla and Joe gasp]
¡Mija! Oh, my God.
[uplifting music playing]
[Carla sobbing]
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- No. No.
No. No.
[Carla and Jenny sobbing]
Levon!
[sobbing]
Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you.
[all crying]
[Joyce] I was thinking
about taking Merry
out to the chicken coop today.
[Gunny] Oh.
- Yeah, would you like that?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
You better watch out
for that old grumpy one.
- [Merry chuckles]
- He's mean. He's mean.
- Oh, no. He's mean.
- [door knob rattles]
Hey, Dad, it's
you! You came back.
[gentle music playing]
Told you I would.
[chuckles, kisses]
You're okay, Daddy?
Yeah. I nicked myself shaving.
Hi.
Welcome back.
[gentle music continues]
Hey, Joyce.
You're in one piece.
Just about.
Well, I guess they
didn't kill you, huh?
Nah. They really
tried their best.
[Gunny] Oh.
You found that girl?
I found her.
So, what did I miss?
Well, I made friends
with a crow and an owl.
And there's a goat I
taught to say my name.
- No.
- Yeah.
It was really cool.
I was just talking,
and then it was like, "Merry!
"Merry!"
[uplifting music playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
Welcome back, brother.
You're home.
[chuckles softly]
[music fades]
[resolute music playing]
[heroic music playing]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]